EDWARD-JOHN MUNA

CONTACT

Tacoma, WA 98445

2532322383

bearmuna@gmail.com

https://github.com/bear-muna

https://react-bearportfolio.netlify.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bear

SKILLS

- Critical Thinking
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- React Software Proficiency
- Excellent Communication
- Flexible and Adaptable
- Organization and Time Management
- CSŠ Proficiency
- Wireframing and Mockup DesignDatabases: Oracle, SQL Server, MongoDB
- Project Management

EDUCATION

June 2023

Full-Stack Developer Certificate Web Development University of Washington, Seattle, WA

Bachelor of Science Biology

University of Washington, Seattle, WA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With a solid understanding / foundation in building end-to-end applications, I aim to enhance the user-experience in the internet economy. My goal is to make it easier for users to achieve their own goals through simple, yet effective application designs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

May 2023 - June 2023

Full Stack Developer (Project Portal) UW Bootcamp Project Three, Seattle, WA

- Assisted users to form teams around various project ideas
- Implemented a server using a mySQL database with React to persist data amongst users
- Worked in teams efficiently to produce a robust, full-stack application within a small time frame
- Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery
- Integrated web-socket for live chat experience

Deployed Link: https://proj-portal.netlify.app/

GitHub Repository (Front-end): https://github.com/linotmike/Projectportal-front-end

GitHub Repository (Back-end): https://github.com/linotmike/projectportal-back-end

April 2023 - May 2023

Full Stack Developer (Bite Buddies) UW Bootcamp Project Two, Seattle,

- Assisted in building a full-stack application that allowed users to connect with one another based on similar interests
- Successfully managed and deployed a robust, full-stack application involving handlebars.js, mySQL, and express.js
- Helped team members with various coding problems in creating project **Deployed Application:** https://bite-buddies.herokuapp.com/ GitHub Repository: https://github.com/bear-muna/bife-buddies

March 2023 - April 2023

Full Stack Developer (Enter The Temple) UW Bootcamp Project One, Seattle, WA

- Assisted in developing front-end application that allowed users be a part of a 'Create Your Own Adventure' story
- Developed front-end logic that allowed users to traverse across various
- Integrated third-party API's in enhance user enjoyment **Deployed Link:** https://solnatis.github.io/Project-One/ GitHub Repository: https://github.com/Solnatis/Project-One